Guide to the CASA Latina Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- PROGRAM FILES [SERIE 5: ARCHIVOS DE PROGRAMAS], 1992-2014; SERIES 5 (Box-folder 1/8, 1/11, 1/14, 1/21, 1/62-65, 1/86, 2/39-61, 2/76-77, 4/3, 4/18, 4/58, 5/2-6, 5/18, 5/9, 5/11, 5/13-14, 5/51, 6/1-21, 7/49, 7/50-52, 8/11-13, 8/17, 8/22, 8/28-32, 8/42-45, 8/52-55, 98-10, 9/12-15, 9/20-25, 9/33, 9/40
  - Education and Literacy Programs [Subserie A: Programas de Educación y Literacia], 1992-2008; Subseries A (Box-folder 1/14, 1/86, 4/18, 4/58, 5/2-4, 5/18, 5/9, 5/13-14, 7/49, 7/51-52, 8/52-53, 9/13, 9/25, 9/43, 9/45, 9/47, 9/49)
    - Ramah Navajo School Training [Entrenamiento de Escuela Ramah Navajo], 1993 (Box-folder 9/45)
    - Participatory Ed Programs/Resources [Programas/Recursos de Educación Participative] (Box-folder 9/47)
    - Seminar Skills [Habilidades de Seminario] (Box-folder 9/49)
    - CASA Latina First Book [Primer Libro CASA Latina], 1999-2001 (Box-folder 5/14)
    - CASA Latina Family Program (NW Children's Fund) [Programa Familiar CASA Latina (Fondo Niñere Noroeste)], 2004 (Box-folder 1/86)
    - CASA Latina Family Literacy Program Evaluation [Evaluación de Programa para Literacidad Familiar CASA Latina], 1999-2001 (Box-folder 5/13)
    - Literacy Outcomes [Resultados de Literacia], 1999 (Box-folder 8/53)
    - Family Literacy Training [Entrenamiento para Literacidad Familiar], 1998 (Box-folder 9/43)
    - Laubach Literacy Action--Maria's Story [Acción Laubach Literaria--Historia de Maria], 1997 (Box-folder 8/52)
    - Child Education of Women's Program [Programa Educativo Niñero de Mujeres], 1998-1999 (Box-folder 4/18)
    - Adult Homeless Education [Educación para Adultos Sin Hogar], 1995 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Adult Education for Homeless Annual Report [Reporte Anual sobre Educación para Adultos Sin Hogar], 1994 (Box-folder 5/9)
    - Volunteer Tutor Coordination Program (1 of 2) [Programa para Coordinar Tutores Voluntaries (1 de 2)], 1992-1996 (Box-folder 5/3)
    - Volunteer Tutor Coordination Program (2 of 2) [Programa para Coordinar Tutores Voluntaries (2 de 2)], 1995-1999 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Volunteer Tutor Coordination Program [Programa para Coordinar Tutores Voluntaries], 1998-1999 (Box-folder 5/18)
    - Liderazgo (Educación Popular) [Leadership (Popular Education)] (Box-folder 7/49)
    - Popular Education Training: Grants, Workshop Evaluations, Camp Long [Entrenamientos para Educación Popular: Subvenciones, Evaluaciones de Taller, Camp Long], 2000-2001 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Taller de Educación Popular [Popular Education Workshop], 2001 (Box-folder 7/51)
    - Popular Education Conference [Conferencia de Educación Popular], 1994-2004 (Box-folder 7/52)
    - Popular Education Conference [Conferencia de Educación Popular], 1999 (Box-folder 9/13)
  - English as a Second Language (ESL) [Subserie B: Inglés como Segundo Idioma (ESL)], 1991-1998; Subseries B (Box-folder 8/11-13, 8/17, 8/45, 8/54, 9/12, 9/14, 9/33, 9/42)
    - Learning Disabilities Resources [Recursos para Discapacidades de Aprendizaje] (Box-folder 8/13)
    - Grammar Workshop - ESL [Taller de Gramática - Inglés como Segunda Lengua] (Box-folder 8/11)
    - Pronunciation Workshop [Taller de Pronunciación] (Box-folder 8/12)
    - Women's ESL Program Evaluation [Evaluación de Programa de Inglés para Mujeres], 1995 (Box-folder 8/45)
    - Survey of ESL Instructional & Assessment Practices [Encuesta de Prácticas de Instrucción y Evaluación de Enseñar Inglés], 1996 (Box-folder 8/54)
    - Focus on Basics Article [Artículo Enfoca en Básicos], 1998 (Box-folder 8/17)
    - Organizing ESL Students for Social Change [Organizando Estudiantes de Inglés para Cambios Sociales], 1997 (Box-folder 9/12)
    - ABLE Workshops--ESL Curriculum [Talleres ABLE--Currículo de Clases de Inglés], 1998 (Box-folder 9/14)
    - ESL Curriculum: A Participatory Curriculum for Farmworkers [Currículo Inglés como Segunda Lengua: Un Currículo Participativo para Trabajadores Agrícoles], 1991 (Box-folder 9/33)
    - ESL: Negotiating a Curriculum [Inglés como Segunda Lengua: Negociando un Currículo], 1993 (Box-folder 9/42)
  - Worker Education and Organizing [Subserie C: Educación y Organización de Trabajadores], 1994-2014; Subseries C (Box-folder 1/8, 1/11, 1/21, 4/3, 6/1-14, 6/17, 6/21, 7/50, 8/42-44, 9/8-10, 9/15, 9/20-24, 9/50, 9/54, 11/36, 11/46-55, 12/1-4, 13/2-3)
    - Participatory Action Research for Day Laborers, Grants [Investigación de Acción Participativa por Jornaleros, Subvenciones], 1998-2002 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Workers' Rights Curriculum [Currículo de Derechos del Trabajador] (Box-folder 9/50)
    - Immigration-Related Employer Obligations [Obligaciones de Empleadores Relacionados a Inmigración], 1998-2009 (Box-folder 9/54)
    - Women's Program & Carolyn Downs [Programa para Mujeres y Carolyn Downs], 2001-2003 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - National Day Laborer Organizing Project [Proyecto Nacional para Organizar Jornaleros], 2000-2003 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Diploma of National Day Organizing Network [Diploma de Red Nacional de Organizadores de Jornaleros], 2002 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Day Laborer Conferences and Resources [Conferencias y Recursos para Jornaleros], 2000-2001 (Box-folder 9/20)
    - Seattle Police Department and Day Laborers [Departamento de Policía de Seattle y Jornaleros], 1998 (Box-folder 9/21)
    - Yard Labor Agreements [Acuerdos de Trabajo de Yarda], 2008 (Box-folder 9/23)
    - Day Laborer Organizing [Organizando por Jornaleros], 2008 (Box-folder 9/24)
    - Agenda Underground Economy in the Construction Industry [Agenda de Economía Clandestina en la Industria de Construcción], 2007 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - MISC Underground Economy in the Construction Industry [MISC Economía Clandestina en la Industria de Construcción], 2007 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - Business Caucus Underground Economy in the Construction Industry [Junta Negociera de Economía Clandestina en la Industria de Construcción], 2007 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Labor Caucus Underground Economy in the Construction Industry [Junta Laboral de Economía Clandestina en la Industria de Construcción, 2007 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - WA Legislature Underground Economy in the Construction [Legislatura WA Economía Clandestina en la Industria de Construcción], 2007 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Labor Industry Underground Economy in the Construction Industry [Industria Laboral Economía Clandestina en la Industria de Construcción], 2007 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Employment SEC. Underground Economy in the Construction Industry [Seguridad de Empleo Economía Clandestina en la Industria de Construcción], 2007 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Individual Contractors Employment [Empleo de Contratistas Individuales], 2007 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Department of Revenue Underground Economy in the Construction Industry [Departamento de Ingresos Economía Clandestina en la Industria de Construcción], 2007 (Box-folder 6/9)
    - Other States Underground Economy in the Construction Industry (1 of 2) [Otros Estados Economía Clandestina en la Industria de Construcción (1 de 2)], 2007 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - Other States Underground Economy in the Construction Industry (2 of 2) [Otros Estados Economía Clandestina en la Industria de Construcción (2 de 2)], 2007 (Box-folder 6/11)
    - 1099 Misclassification: It's Time To Play By The Blues [Clasificación Errónea 1099: Es Tiempo de Jugar por Los Azules], 2007 (Box-folder 6/12)
    - Taxpayer Impact of Worsening Employment Practices in New York City's Construction Industry [Impacto de Empeoramiento de Prácticas de Empleo de Ciudad Nueva York a Contribuyentes], 2007 (Box-folder 6/13)
    - Report of Workers Compensation Premium Status for Wood Floor Contraction Services in WA [Informe Sobre Compensación Laboral Estado Premium por Servicios Contratados para Pisos de Madera en WA], 2007 (Box-folder 6/14)
    - Summary of Independent Contractor Reforms State and Federal Activity [Sumario de Reformes de Contratistas Independientes al Nivel Estatal y Federal], 2008 (Box-folder 6/21)
    - Documents of Department of Labor & Industries [Documentos del Departamento de Trabajo e Industria], 2008 (Box-folder 6/17)
    - Workplace Project--Long Island, NY [Proyecto de Lugar de Trabajo--Long Island, NY], 1995 (Box-folder 8/42)
    - Contingent Labor Forum [Foro Sobre Trabajo Contingente], 2003 (Box-folder 8/43)
    - Domestic/Dating Violence Handbook [Manual sobre Violencia Doméstica/Íntima], 1994 (Box-folder 8/44)
    - Construction: Andersen Construction Company [Construcción: Anderson Construction Company], 2011-2013 (Box-folder 11/46)
    - Construction: OAC meetings [Construcción: Juntas OAC], 2012 (Box-folder 11/47)
    - Construction: Change Orders [Construcción: Cambios al Orden], 2011-2013 (Box-folder 11/48)
    - Construction: Punch List Correspondence [Construcción: Correspondencia Sobre Lista de Tareas], 2012-2013 (Box-folder 11/49)
    - Construction: Architectural Drawings [Construcción: Dibujos Arquitectónicos] (Box-folder 11/50)
    - Construction: Vertical Visual Solutions [Construcción: Soluciones Visuales Verticales], 2012-2013 (Box-folder 11/51)
    - Construction: Metzker Communications [Construcción: Comunicaciones Metzker], 2013 (Box-folder 11/52)
    - Construction: Budgets [Construcción: Presupuestos], 2012-2013 (Box-folder 11/53)
    - Construction: Misc. [Construcción: Misc.], 2011-2013 (Box-folder 11/54)
    - Construction: Express Construction [Construcción: Construcción Rápido] (Box-folder 11/55)
    - Seattle Construction Careers Advisory Committee Information Binder--Part 1 of 4 [Carpeta de Información del Comité Consultivo sobre Carreras de Construcción en Seattle--Parte 1 de 4], 2013-2014 (Box-folder 12/1)
    - Seattle Construction Careers Advisory Committee Information Binder--Part 2 of 4 [Carpeta de Información del Comité Consultivo sobre Carreras de Construcción en Seattle--Parte 2 de 4], 2013-2014 (Box-folder 12/2)
    - Seattle Construction Careers Advisory Committee Information Binder--Part 3 of 4 [Carpeta de Información del Comité Consultivo sobre Carreras de Construcción en Seattle--Parte 3 de 4], 2013-2014 (Box-folder 12/3)
    - Seattle Construction Careers Advisory Committee Information Binder--Part 4 of 4 [Carpeta de Información del Comité Consultivo sobre Carreras de Construcción en Seattle--Parte 4 de 4], 2013-2014 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Underground Economy Task Force--Part 1 of 2 [Fuerza Especial de Economía Clandestina--Parte 1 de 2], 2009 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - Underground Economy Task Force--Part 2 of 2 [Fuerza Especial de Economía Clandestina--Parte 2 de 2], 2009 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Street Theater Outline [Esbozo de Teatro Callejero], 1995 (Box-folder 7/50)
    - CASA Latina Proposal to Organize Street Day Laborers Outside Home Depot [Propuesta Para Organizar Trabajadores Fuera Home Depot], 2005 (Box-folder 11/36)
    - Street Outreach Volunteer Training [Entrenamiento de Voluntarios de Alcance Callejera], 1994 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Street Outreach Services Class [Clase de Servicios por Alcance Callejera], 1996 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - Street Outreach Services Agreement [Contrato de Servicios por Alcance Callejera], 1996 (Box-folder 9/10)
    - Nine West Settlement Proposal (Declined) [Propuesta de Liquidación Nine West (Rechazado)], 2000 (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Immigrant Rights [Subserie D: Derechos de Inmigrantes], 1996-2009; Subseries D (Box-folder 10/4, 10/13-14, 10/22-29, 10/38-39, 11/10)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride [Viaje por La Libertad de Trabajadores Migrantes], 2003 (Box-folder 10/4)
    - US Congressional Immigration Reform Act [Acto para Reforma Migratoria del Congreso Estadounidense], 2006 (Box-folder 10/13)
    - National Immigration Forum [Foro Nacional sobre Inmigración], 2008 (Box-folder 10/14)
    - Immigration Status--San Francisco Administrative Code [Estado de Inmigración--Código Administrativo San Francisco] (Box-folder 10/22)
    - Immigration Raids [Redadas por Inmigración], 2004 (Box-folder 10/23)
    - Low-income Immigrant Rights Conference [Conferencia sobre Derechos de Inmigrantes de Bajos Recursos], 2005 (Box-folder 10/24)
    - Immigration Law [Ley de Inmigración], 2000 (Box-folder 10/25)
    - Immigration Rights/Legalization [Derechos de Inmigración/Legalización] (Box-folder 10/26)
    - Immigration Workshop [Taller de Inmigración], 2000 (Box-folder 10/27)
    - "Jose, Can You See Me?" by Samuel Huntington ["¿Jose, Me Puedes Ver?" por Samuel Huntington] (Box-folder 10/28)
    - Legal Issues Serving Undocumented Student [Cuestiones Legales en Sirviendo a los Estudiantes Indocumentados], 1998 (Box-folder 10/29)
    - Immigrants in the Workplace Training Materials and Information Resources, approximately 1999 (Box-folder 10/38)
    - Immigration Legislation Reform Information, approximately 1996-2006 (Box-folder 10/39)
    - Race & Social Justice Project: Conference for Latino Immigrant Women in Seattle [Proyecto sobre Raza y Justicia Social: Conferencia para Mujeres Inmigrantes Latinas en Seattle], 2006 (Box-folder 11/10)
  - Legislative Advocacy and Lobbying [Subserie E: Cabildeo y Defensa Legislativa], 1997-2009; Subseries E (Box-folder 6/15-20, 8/22, 8/28-32, 8/55, 9/40)
    - Joint Legislative Task Force of Memorandum [Grupo de Trabajo Legislativo Conjunto de Memorándum], 2008 November 4 (Box-folder 6/15)
    - OCT Conference of Joint Legislative Task Force [Conferencia OCT del Grupo de Trabajo Legislativo], 2008 (Box-folder 6/16)
    - May Conference of Joint Legislative Task Force [Conferencia de Mayo del Grupo de Trabajo Legislativo], 2008 (Box-folder 6/18)
    - Benchmark Advisory Committee [Comité Consultivo sobre Punto de Referencia], 2008 (Box-folder 6/19)
    - Extra Information of Joint Legislative Task Force [Información Extra del Grupo de Trabajo Legislativo], 2008 (Box-folder 6/20)
    - State Lobbying [Cabildeo Estatal], 2009 (Box-folder 8/22)
    - Olympia Lobbying Packets [Paquetes de Cabildeo en Olympia], 2007 (Box-folder 8/28)
    - Senate Budget Request [Solicitud de Propuesto al Senado], 2006 (Box-folder 8/29)
    - House Budget Request [Solicitud de Presupuesto a la Casa de Representantes], 2007 (Box-folder 8/30)
    - Guide to Participating in Washington Legislature [Guía de Participación en La Legislatura Washington], 2006 (Box-folder 8/31)
    - City Budget Process [Proceso del Presupuesto Ciudadal], 2005 (Box-folder 8/32)
    - Lobbying for Literacy [Cabildeo por Literacia], 1997 (Box-folder 8/55)
    - Lobbying State Legislature [Cabildeando a Legislatura Estatal], 2009 (Box-folder 9/40)
  - Capacity Building Programs [Subserie F: Programas para Crecer Capacidad], 1993-2009; Subseries F (Box-folder 1/62-65, 2/39-61, 2/76-77, 5/5-6, 5/11, 5/51, 11/3-9)
    - Strategic Fundraising Plan of Hispanic Capacity [Plan Estratégico para Recaudar Fondos de Capacidad Hispana], 2004-2009 (Box-folder 1/62)
    - Hispanic Capacity Project correspondence [Correspondencia de Proyecto Capacidad Hispana], 2004 March (Box-folder 1/63)
    - Hispanic Capacity Project (1 of 2) [Proyecto Capacidad Hispana (1 de 2)], 2003-2004 (Box-folder 1/64)
    - Hispanic Capacity project (2 of 2) [Proyecto Capacidad Hispana (2 de 2)], 2004 (Box-folder 1/65)
    - Hispanic Capacity [Capacidad Hispana], 2003 (Box-folder 2/76)
    - Hispanic Capacity [Capacidad Hispana], 2003-2004 (Box-folder 2/77)
    - Hispanic Capacity Project Report [Informe sobre Proyecto Capacidad Hispana], 2004-2005 (Box-folder 3/39)
    - United Way Contract (1 of 3) [Contrato United Way (1 de 3)], 2002-2003 (Box-folder 2/40)
    - United Way Contract (2 of 3) [Contrato United Way (2 de 3)], 2002-2003 (Box-folder 2/41)
    - United Way Contract (3 of 3) [Contrato United Way (3 de 3)], 2002-2003 (Box-folder 2/42)
    - The Plan of United Way Data Collection [Plan de Colectar Datos de United Way], 2003-2004 (Box-folder 2/43)
    - The United Way Data Collection [Datos Colectados United Way], 2005-2006 (Box-folder 2/44)
    - United Way Demographic Data [Datos Demográficos United Way], 2001-2005 (Box-folder 2/45)
    - United Way Eligibility [Elegibilidad United Way], 2000-2002 (Box-folder 2/46)
    - United Way Eligibility Forms [Formularios de Elegibilidad United Way], 1998-2001 (Box-folder 2/47)
    - CASA Latina Family Program (NW Children's Fund) [Programa Familiar CASA Latina (Fondo Niñero Noroeste)], 2001-2002 (Box-folder 2/48)
    - United Way Project Lift-Off [Proyecto Despegue United Way], 2002-2003 (Box-folder 2/49)
    - United Way Donor Designation [Designacion de Donantes United Way], 2000-2001 (Box-folder 2/50)
    - United Way Day of Caring [Día de Cuidado United Way], 2002 (Box-folder 2/51)
    - United Way Day of King County [Día de Condado King United Way], 2004-2005 (Box-folder 2/52)
    - Community Safety Net Outcome Report [Informe de Resultados de Red de Seguridad Comunitaria], 2000-2001 (Box-folder 2/53)
    - United Way Outcome Reports [Informes de Resultados United Way], 2000-2001 (Box-folder 2/54)
    - United Way Outcomes [Resultados United Way], 2001-2002 (Box-folder 2/55)
    - United Way Outcomes [Resultados United Way], 2002-2003 (Box-folder 2/56)
    - United Way Outcomes [Resultados United Way], 2003 (Box-folder 2/57)
    - United Way Outcomes [Resultados United Way], 2003-2004 (Box-folder 2/58)
    - United Way Outcomes [Resultados United Way], 2004-2005 (Box-folder 2/59)
    - United Way Proposal [Propuesta United Way], 2000 (Box-folder 2/60)
    - United Way Proposal [Propuesta United Way], 2002-2004 (Box-folder 2/61)
    - United Way of King County (1 of 2) [United Way de Condado King (1 de 2)], 1995-1996 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - United Way of King County (2 of 2) [United Way de Condado King (2 de 2)], 1995-1996; . (Box-folder 5/6)
    - United Way of King County (Education of the Outcomes of Funding) [United Way de Condado King (Resultados de Uso de Fondos)], 1993-1994 (Box-folder 5/11)
    - United Way Review [Revisión United Way], 1996 (Box-folder 5/51)
    - United Way Proposal [Propuesta United Way], 2005-2007 (Box-folder 11/3)
    - United Way Alexis De Toqueville Tour, 2006 (Box-folder 11/4)
    - United Way Contract [Contrato United Way], 2005-2006 (Box-folder 11/5)
    - United Way Outcomes [Resultados United Way], 2006-2007 (Box-folder 11/6)
    - United Way Para Los Ninos, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 11/7)
    - United Way Contract [Contrato United Way], 2006-2007 (Box-folder 11/8)
    - United Way Outcomes [Contrato United Way], 2005-2006 (Box-folder 11/9)
- CONTRACTS AND AGREEMENTS [SERIE 6: CONTRATOS Y ACUERDOS], 1993-2010; SERIES 6 (Box-folder 1/1-7, 1/9-10, 1/12, 1/15-16, 1/18, 1/25, 1/27-29, 1/31-36, 1/42-44, 1/48-49, 1/59-61, 1/66, 1/87, 2/7, 2/12-13, 2/16-26, 2/28, 2/34-38, 2/62, 2/68-74, 4/24, 4/34, 4/44, 5/17, 5/23, 5/25, 5/32, 5/34, 5/36-39, 5/42, 5/50, 5/55-56, 5/58-59, 5/60-1, 6/22, 7/2, 7/9, 7/15, 7/43-46, 8/14-16, 8/33-36, 8/46, 8/61, 9/1-5, 9/16-18, 9/22, 9/29, 9/39, 9/51-52, 10/12, 10/32, 10/34, 11/2, 11/23, 11/36)
  Grant proposals, service agreements, and funding agreements. May relate to the financial records in SERIES 4, Subseries B and some of the organizations in SERIES 9. [Propuestas para subvenciones de fundación, acuerdos de servicio y acuerdos de fundación. Relacionado a registros financieros en SERIE 4, Subserie B y organizaciones en SERIE 9].
  - Agreement for Attorney Services, Hilary Stern [Acuerdo para Servicios de Abogado, Hilary Stern], 2003 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - A Territory Resource (ATR) Donor Advised Grant [Un Recurso Territorial (ATR) Subvención Aconsejado por Donor], 2005 (Box-folder 1/15)
  - A Territory Resource (ATR) Donor Advised Grant [Un Recurso Territorial (ATR) Subvención Aconsejado por Donor], 2004 (Box-folder 1/16)
  - A Territory Resource (ATR) Three Year Capacity Building program [Un Recurso Territorial (ATR) Programa para Crecer Capacidad sobre Tres Años], 1999-2002 (Box-folder 1/18)
  - A Territory Resource (ATR) Year-End Evaluation [A Territory Resource (ATR) Evaluación Fin de Año], 1998 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Aaron & Rachael Contorer Grants [Subvenciones Aaron & Rachael Contorer], 1998-1999 (Box-folder 5/39)
  - Adult Education Act Grant [Subvención Acto de Educación de Adultos], 1996-1998 (Box-folder 5/38)
  - Adult Education Grant [Subvención de Educación para Adultos], 1995-1997 (Box-folder 5/58)
  - Agreement for Shared Costs of Racism Training [Acuerdo por Costo Compartido de Entrenamiento de Deshacer el Racismo], 2003 (Box-folder 1/25)
  - Amicus Brief in Champagne v. Thurston County [Breve Amicus en Caso de Condado Champagne v. Condado Thurston], 2007 (Box-folder 8/14)
  - Application--Letter of Inquiry, PGA [Solicitud--Carta de Consulta, PGA], 2005 (Box-folder 2/18)
  - Art Basic Grant, PLNDH [Subvención Básica de Arte], 2005 (Box-folder 2/13)
  - ATR (A Territory Resource) Grant Application [Un Recurso Territorial (ATR) Solicitud para Subvención ], 1998 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - ATR Cultural Grant [Subvención Cultural ATR], 1997-1999 (Box-folder 5/23)
  - ATR Fall Application [Aplicación ATR Otoño], 1998 (Box-folder 5/61)
  - ATR Fall-Organizing Laborers [ATR Otoño-Organizando Obreres], 1998 (Box-folder 5/42)
  - ATR Grants Paper (1 of 2) [Documento Subvenciones ATR (1 de 2)], 1996-1998 (Box-folder 5/55)
  - ATR Grants Paper (2 of 2) [Documento Subvenciones ATR (2 de 2)], 1994-1996 (Box-folder 5/56)
  - ATR Major Grant Pre Application [Pre-aplicación para Subvención Mayor ATR], 1997 (Box-folder 5/50)
  - ATR Major Grant Program [Programa de Subvenciones Mayores ATR], 1996-1999 (Box-folder 5/37)
  - ATR Technical Assistance Grant [Subvención ATR Asistencia Técnica], 1998-2000 (Box-folder 5/17)
  - CASA Latina, PWF [CASA Latina, PWF], 2003-2004 (Box-folder 2/20)
  - Certification of Enrollment [Certificado de Inscripción], 2009 July 26 (Box-folder 6/22)
  - Champagne v. Thurston County [Condados Champagne Contra Thurston], 2007 (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Citizenship Training Contract with State (Part 1 of 2) [Contrato Estadal para Formación Ciudadana (Parte 1 de 2)], 1997 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Citizenship Training Contract with State (Part 2 of 2) [Contrato Estadal para Formación Ciudadana (Parte 2 de 2)], 1997 (Box-folder 9/5)
  - City Contract (w/Northwest Immigrant Rights Project [Contrato Ciudadal (con El Proyecto para los Derechos del Inmigrante)], 1995 (Box-folder 8/34)
  - City Contract [Contrato Ciudadal], 1997 (Box-folder 8/33)
  - City Contract [Contrato Ciudadal], 2007 (Box-folder 11/37)
  - City Light Property, Substation [City Light, Propiedad, Subestación], 2004 (Box-folder 1/44)
  - City Light, Substation, Insurance [City Light, Subestación, Aseguranza], 2002 (Box-folder 1/43)
  - City of Seattle Contract [Contrato con Ciudad de Seattle], 1999 (Box-folder 5/25)
  - City of Seattle Contract Assessment [Evaluación del Contrato con Ciudad Seattle], 2009 (Box-folder 9/39)
  - City of Seattle: Contract & Program Standards [Ciudad Seattle: Estándares de Contratos y Programas], 2003-2004 (Box-folder 1/32)
  - City of Seattle: Contract Details [Ciudad Seattle: Detalles de Contrato], 2000 (Box-folder 1/35)
  - City of Seattle: Contract Processing & Report [Ciudad Seattle: Informe y Proceso de Contrato], 2005 (Box-folder 1/31)
  - City of Seattle: Contract Renewal & Agreements [Ciudad Seattle: Acuerdos & Renovación de Contrato], 2002-2003 (Box-folder 1/33)
  - City of Seattle: Contracts & Budgeting [Ciudad Seattle: Contratos & Presupuestos], 2001-2002 (Box-folder 1/34)
  - City of Seattle: Project Services Agreement [Ciudad Seattle: Acuerdo de Servicios de Proyectos], 1999-2000 (Box-folder 1/36)
  - City of Seattle: Project Services Agreements & Contracts [Ciudad Seattle: Acuerdo de Servicios y Contratos], 2005-2006 (Box-folder 1/29)
  - Computer Equipment (Seattle Foundation) [Equipo de Computadors (Fundación Seattle)], 2000 (Box-folder 2/37)
  - Consultant Contracts [Contratos de Consultorios], 2005-2006 (Box-folder 8/15)